**Arthur Harutyunyan** 

Current Company: "CloudSideTech" LLC

Job Title: QA Manager

Summary: Enthusiastic and experienced QA engineer and Technical Leader with hands-on

experience in Quality assurance and Testing over the last 10 years. Proven skills in

communication, leadership, management and problem-solving. Always eager to learn new

technologies and frameworks, change and adapt to new environments. Coaching and managing

the team to grow to upper levels, efficiently managing projects and always applying new

methodologies and technologies towards the best delivery of the qualified products.

Phone Number: +374 93 70 99 44

E-mail: a.harutyunyan.a@gmail.com

**Experience** 

March 2016 - Present

Company: "CloudSideTech" LLC

Position: QA Manager

Responsibilities:

As Software Developer Engineer in Test +

Established and implemented test automation framework from the scratch using e2e test

automation tool Cypress with Javascript

Created automated test scripts for different websites and web applications both on

mobile and desktop versions like:

o Online gaming platforms. The company develops websites with different

third-party integrations

Backoffice tools to support/manage and maintain the platforms from point above

Have an experience with API test automation using Cypress

Setting up and managing the whole automation pipeline using Jenkins pipelines Also

have an experience with GitHub Actions and Bitbucket Pipelines

- Automating also the deployment pipelines on different UNIX-based server infrastructure using Jenkins as CI/CD.
- Creating scripts on Javascript to generate test-data from the Back-End for the QA team

### As QA Manager

- Established, implemented, and improved QA test procedures, process, and quality standards in accordance with overall development and product releases.
- Supervised and led a team of QA engineers up to 5 QA members to ensure quality of the product releases.
- Responsible for the daily activities of the QA staff assigned to various and multiple projects. Monitor the successful completion of the quality initiatives at every step of the SDLC.
- Encouraged collaboration and growth of individual QA team members to take ownership
  of features. To make this more efficient, organizing small trainings with the QA team on
  different QA topics.
- Responsible for creating and managing QA Projects, Priorities, Resource allocation.
- Retrospective meetings after the project/product delivery.
- The full JIRA administration. Setting up JIRA projects along with its permission and workflow schemes. Creating, maintaining the whole JIRA workflows along with the JIRA boards, sprints, backlogs. Creating different reports using additional JIRA plugins and many more.

## As Product/Project Manager:

- Requirement analysis with the customers and business partners.
- Discussing the project scope with different stakeholders.
- Organizing technical and requirement analysis collaboration with the Dev and QA team to come up with the ETAs.
- Organizing and managing the whole SDLC in JIRA started from task creating-distributing to corresponding dev teams, creating and managing the 2-3 weeks sprints.
- Planning the project scope with the dev team and follow-up there are no deviations from the plan.
- Organizing daily meetings with the team to make sure we are on the same page and there is no deviation from the planned delivery.
- Providing the "state of the union" to different business partners and other stakeholders.
- Creating "Release Notes" for the customers.

#### Tools/Skills:

- JIRA, Confluence, Bitbucket Project management and bug tracking toolset
- Postman, API testing (Cypress)
- Qase.io, TestRail test management tools
- Jenkins, .git, GitHub Actions, Bitbucket Pipelines devops tools
- Starpi (CMS), MySQL, MongoDB databases and content management system
- Javascript programming language used in test automation
- Cypress.io test automation tool

May 2014 - March 2016

Company: "Wiblar Zone" LLC

Position: Junior QA

## Responsibilities:

Analyzing requirements.

- Performed manual testing on web and desktop download applications.
- Communicated with the development team and documented all the bugs discovered during the testing.
- Performed System, Integration and UI testing on multiple web-based products and platforms.
- Review functional and design specifications.

#### Tools:

- Assembla as a bug tracking system.
- Jenkins as Ci/CD.
- Testlink for test-case management.

Apr-2011 - May-2014
Company: "Cross Net" LLC
Position: Network Administrator

Responsibilities:

Assisted in network design and implementation,

- Install and configure computer network equipment.
- Maintain network connectivity of computer workstations, VoIP, internet TV services.
- Provide network support to "Zvartnots" International Airport cooperative users. Monitor network to ensure optimal performance.

\_\_\_\_\_

## **Education**

2003-2007 | Yerevan State University of Armenia

Bachelor's degree in Informatics and Applied Mathematics

# **Languages**

Armenian: Native

Russian: Fluent

English: Fluent